Still messing with my uke?
I'm not messing with it.
I'm just, you know, trying to
teach myself how to play it.
- Well, you have to make a chord.
- Chord?
Take this finger right
there, put it on that string.
- Like that? Okay.
- Yeah.
- Take that finger and put it there.
- Like that?
All right, now, play the four.
- The four of them?
- Mm-hm.
See? That's the C chord.
- Hey!
- Ha-ha.
- How about that?
- Heh-heh.
- Did Will call?
- No, he didn't.
He's late.
Well... Well, he's
only four minutes late.
I can't wait to get
out to that lake.
We've already picked out
- our favorite spot and everything.
- Oh...
Will you get that?
- Yeah. Oh, yeah.
- Careful.
I'll treat it as if
it were my own.
- Yeah.
- There you go.
Coming.
- Oh, Ben.
- Hey, Ben.
- What happened?
- Well, I got mugged last night.
- What?
- Well, I don't know who it was.
Came up behind me and whacked
me on the arm with a crowbar,
took my wallet and ran off.
Well, that's awful.
Ben, I know how much you
really wanted to go on this trip.
If I thought I could
fish left-handed, heh...
Well, there's always next year.
I'm sorry, Ben.
Take care of your arm.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, I'll see you, Will.
- See you.
- See you, Will.
Oh...
That's gotta hurt.
What do you look
so dejected for?
You know, you
can still go fishing.
I don't wanna fish by myself.
Oh, don't you remember?
I told you yesterday.
One of Judge Stern's
law clerks called.
He invited you to go
out on his boat tomorrow.
You know, Judge Stern's
invited me a hundred times
and I've never been able to go.
Well, give him a call.
- Hi, guys.
- Oh, hey, Jer.
Well, uh, I thought you'd
be long gone by now.
Tomorrow.
I'm going fishing on
Judge Stern's boat.
I thought you got
seasick on boats.
Oh, no, that was
a long time ago.
- Ben.
- Huh?
Here's some soda water. Drink
some of that and you'll be all right.
- Get your sea legs back in no time.
- Okay.
Now, Ben, would you
mind if I went back out there
for about 30 minutes?
My boat's been in dry dock
for a week getting painted,
and I sure would like
to do a little more fishing.
- Go ahead.
- You'll be all right?
I'll be all right.
- Glen Silver?
- Yeah.
I'm Detective Marks.
This is Officer Brown.
I'd like to ask you
a few questions.
What's this about, detective?
Were you at the
marina yesterday?
- Yeah. Why?
- Did you happen to see
Judge Michael Stern
while you were there?
Judge Stern?
- What are you talking about?
- Straightforward question.
Did you see Judge Stern yesterday
when you were at the marina?
I'm not answering till you
tell me what this is about.
Judge Stern was killed in an
explosion on his boat yesterday.
I haven't seen the
judge in over four years.
Why are you asking me this?
We found your fingerprints
near the slip where
the judge kept his boat.
- What?
- What do you say
we talk a little more
about this downtown?
Hi, Mr. Matlock.
Oh, hi, Rick.
I'm still in a state of shock.
Yeah, we all are.
- This is, uh...
- Oh, I'm Cliff Lewis.
Hi. Rick Petkin.
Judge Stern's law clerk.
You know, I didn't even think the
judge was taking his boat out this week.
He said he was
getting it painted.
Well, if he wasn't
gonna take the boat out,
why did you call Cliff and tell
me he wanted me to go fishing?
You know, you don't
sound like the guy I talked to.
I wasn't. I didn't call you.
Well, maybe it was one of
Judge Stern's other law clerks.
No, I'm it.
Now, Ben, I'm not delusional.
I know someone from Judge
Stern's law office called me up,
said they were his clerk, and
invited you out on that boat.
Well, somebody
wanted me on that boat.
Why are you so interested
in the guy who mugged me?
Well, Will, I got a kind of a sick
feeling that the explosion on that boat
was meant for me
and not the judge.
Get out of here.
And if it was meant for me,
then somebody had to know
that you and I were going fishing.
In order to get me on that boat,
they had to make sure
we did not go to the lake.
What are you saying, Ben?
I mean, the guy who
broke my arm did it
just so that you'd go
fishing with somebody else?
You didn't even get a glimpse
of the guy that whacked you?
He told me if I
turned around, I'd die.
And I didn't wanna die.
Hm. Yeah.
What did his voice sound like?
Well, it was kind of raspy, I
remember, and a little high.
I'd gotten a call from the
head of Human Resources
- at D.C. Drake Corp.
- Hm.
He said his name
was, uh, Don Arnold.
The company sells
boating equipment.
Well, he said a friend of
mine recommended me
for a sales job in the company
and he wanted to discuss it
over lunch down at the marina.
Did you call your friend
to verify if he did it?
I wasn't about to look a gift
horse in the mouth, Mr. Matlock.
I haven't worked in a long time.
So you met him for lunch?
Yeah. He seemed like a nice guy.
- So much for my judge of character.
- Hm.
So we had lunch and we
took a walk down by the dock.
What did he look like?
Nice-looking guy,
very muscular, um,
blond hair.
- Looked like he'd just gotten it cut.
- Hm.
What about his voice?
It's funny you
should mention that.
I remember thinking that
he had a very high voice.
Mr. Matlock, five years ago,
when Judge Stern had me disbarred
for jury tampering, I hated him.
I was very vocal about it.
I was just angry
that I got caught.
The years of law school,
the indignity of it all and...
I know you didn't
kill the judge, Glen.
But whoever framed you
really did his homework,
killing the judge on the
anniversary of your disbarment.
Somebody must have really
wanted to kill Judge Stern.
Unless I miss my guess,
this had nothing to
do with Judge Stern.
- What?
- I think whoever blew up that boat
had something else
in mind altogether.
Killing me.
If somebody wanted you
dead, Ben, wouldn't it be easier
just to shoot you down or
poison you or something?
What a way to talk.
Oh, you know what I'm saying.
He would've had to
make all those phone calls,
pretend to be a law clerk,
get you on the judge's boat
and then frame Glen Silver.
Mm, mm, mm. Uh-uh.
I think it had to be
more than one person.
You know, think about it.
Because this muscular
guy with this high voice,
he would've had to have
attacked Will, set up Glen Silver
and kill Judge Stern.
It doesn't make sense.
You tell me how
many killers out there
would take a guy to lunch
they're gonna be framing.
I think the guy
Glen had lunch with
works for whoever
blew up the judge's boat.
- Mm, yeah. Yeah.
- A long calculated plan
- that took months to get together.
- Mm.
I've got a lot of enemies.
Fortunately, most of
them are in jail. Ha-ha-ha.
What if one of them
isn't, you know?
What if someone's
on parole or escaped?
Let me look into
that, all right?
Well, yeah, thanks. Yeah.
Yeah, I've been checking out
all the barbershops in the area.
Muscular guy with blond
hair and a high voice?
Mm-hm. He might have
gotten his hair cut here,
like, last Tuesday or Wednesday?
- Is something wrong?
- No. Your hair is just a little stringy.
My hair is not stringy.
Do you remember cutting a
guy's hair that fits that description?
No, but one of my guys is
out sick with the flu today.
- He might have cut it. I could call him.
- Well, here's my business card.
You can call me at that number.
- What?
- Nothing.
Uh, you really like bangs, huh?
They'll probably
make a comeback.
Ben, what do you think
of the way I wear my hair?
It's okay.
Okay?
Yeah, I like
old-fashioned hairdos.
Ben, Ben, Wayne Drummond was
released from prison four months ago.
- Who's Wayne Drummond?
- Oh, he got out, huh?
Yeah. He must have had a
friend on the parole board.
- Who's Wayne Drummond?
- He really hates him.
Who's Wayne Drummond?
Uh, he's a bad actor
who turned killer.
Oh, that Wayne Drummond.
A while back, Leanne and I
stayed at the Wilmont Hotel
for a cousin's wedding.
It turns out I got sick
as a dog that night
and spent the whole
weekend in my hotel room.
I was having trouble
sleeping that first night
and just by chance took a
peek outside my window.
In a house across from the hotel, I
saw a young guy fighting with a girl.
They were at each
other pretty good.
But it was their business,
and I wasn't about
to stick my nose in it.
A little while later, I
happened by the window again,
and I saw what turned out to be
this girl's husband coming home.
The moment he drove up,
the boy inside
hightailed it out of there.
The next morning, I found
out the girl had been murdered.
What in the world is
going on down there?
I don't know.
But that's the house I was
telling you about last night
where I saw that fight.
Looks like the
medical examiner's car.
And so you were
acquainted with the deceased,
- were you?
- Yeah, but...
- Who died?
- Helene Cameron.
Uh, dark hair, mid-30s?
Yeah.
The police say she
was stabbed in the back.
Dad.
I think that's her husband.
He's being arrested.
That's not the man I saw
fighting with her last night.
- It's not?
- No.
I think they got the wrong guy.
You're looking mighty pretty.
The kid I'd seen fighting
with Helene Cameron
was Wayne Drummond,
a wannabe actor.
When I saw him rehearsing
the play he was in,
well, I got a sinking
feeling in my stomach.
Oh!
Dad.
- They were rehearsing that scene.
- Yeah.
Mr. Drummond, I'd like you to
meet my father, Ben Matlock.
- Hi.
- I saw you
at, uh, Helene Cameron's
house the night she died.
Were you working on this scene?
Yeah. That's her understudy.
I guess that's what made it,
uh, look like you were fighting.
The scene.
How much did you see?
Did Helene break
up with you that night?
- No.
- Did she tell you
she was never
gonna see you again?
We were making plans to
spend the weekend together
when her husband
went out of town.
Who told you she
was going to end it?
Her husband? Is
that what he said?
He said that he and Helene
were gonna put their
marriage back together.
That's a lie.
I loved Helene and she loved me.
She was alive when I left.
Leanne ended up defending
Helene Cameron's
husband, Phillip.
Turned out Wayne Drummond
hated Phillip Cameron
from when he was doing
another play several years ago.
- You killed her, didn't you?
- No, I did not.
Yes, you did.
And for the life of me, I
could not figure out why.
I mean, why would
you do such a thing?
Why would you date a married
woman, over two months ago
take out a life insurance
policy in her husband's name
in order to frame him?
Do I have to listen to these
wild accusations, Your Honor?
Not if she doesn't have proof.
Miss Mclntyre?
- I have proof, Your Honor.
- Proceed.
This play that you
were doing in Porterville,
Cat on a Hot Tin Roof,
it had to close, didn't it?
Yes.
Would you tell the court why?
A few days into the play,
there was a car accident,
and one of the
cast members died.
Her name was Carla Waters.
Yes.
You were in love
with her, weren't you?
And Phillip Cameron was
driving the car that hit her.
Okay, it's true. I was in
love with Carla Waters.
This is a copy of the play
taken this morning by
warrant from your house.
You'll notice that all
of the dialogue in here
that is highlighted
is for Helene's role.
Well, I guess I
picked up her copy.
You'll also notice that on
page 14 there are blood stains,
which the medical
examiner has identified
as Helene Cameron's blood.
Oh, come on, you saw the
scene we had to do in that play,
and so did your father. And
he thought I was killing her.
I remember. I had accidentally hit her
in the nose and she got a nosebleed.
Not according to the medical
examiner who did the autopsy.
There was no blood
anywhere near Helene's face,
no cuts on her body at all,
except for the wound that killed her.
So maybe it happened
the night before.
We rehearsed the
scene for a week.
I... I don't remember.
That's not possible either.
You see, as it turns out,
Helene bought a new script
the morning that she died.
So the only way those blood
stains could've gotten on that script
was when you killed her.
Mr. Drummond, this
was a cold murderous act.
You didn't kill out
of passion or hate.
In order to get back
at Phillip Cameron,
you killed somebody
you didn't even dislike.
Well, he certainly sounds
like the type to hold a grudge.
Hello?
Yeah.
He did.
What was the name?
Great. Thank you. Bye.
- That was my barber friend.
- Hm?
Our soprano muscle
man now has a name.
Ty Foster.
Ty... Ty Foster, huh?
Come on, folks, just stay back.
Mr. Foster! This is the
police! Open the door!
If this is your guy with
the high-pitched voice,
you're not gonna hear it.
Nothing. Not one single lead.
Well, that's the way
it goes sometimes.
Maybe Forensics will come up
with something in the morning.
- See you tomorrow.
- Have a good night.
Did you call the police?
There's no need.
Ben, you gotta call the police.
I know who broke
in here last night.
It was Jeffrey Spidel.
That's why there were no
clues over at Ty Foster's place.
That was him too.
Jeffrey Spidel broke in
this house two years ago
and tried to strangle me.
I just learned this
morning he's out of prison.
Hi.
Jeffrey, what are
you doing here?
You slipped off last night
before I could tell you
to have a good day.
You are something. Heh.
- Yeah.
- Ooh.
- Thank you.
- Hey. Mm...
Jeffrey Spidel was one of
the most charming, likable men
you'd ever wanna meet,
except for one thing.
He was a cold-blooded
serial killer.
- What are you doing?
- I don't wanna leave any fingerprints.
No, Jeffrey!
I met him after he
strangled Patricia Downey,
a senior partner in
my accountant's firm.
I figured Spidel must
have really hated her.
I was wrong.
The person he
really hated was me.
- Yes, we had a wonderful evening.
- Sure you didn't have a big argument?
Of course I'm sure.
She didn't lock herself
in the bathroom?
- Where did you get such an idea?
- I've got to ask you where you were
the morning Patricia
Downey was murdered.
I can't believe you...
I really don't have time for
this. I hate to be blunt with you,
but I'm gonna have to ask
you to leave right now. Please.
This makes you
look awfully guilty.
Yes, Mr. Matlock,
I know.
He knew exactly what I'd do
and used it to humiliate me.
And she's all set to testify
that she saw your car
parked in front
of Patricia's house
at 7:15 the morning
she was murdered.
- It couldn't have been my car.
- A black Jaguar XJS convertible
parked right on the street,
just like always, by one of
Patricia's water sprinklers.
That was your car.
You parked it there.
Then you went inside and
you killed her, didn't you?
My car was in the
shop that morning, sir.
What?
My car was in the shop
that morning getting serviced.
They picked it up the
day before the murder,
they returned it to
me the day after.
Call Doug Harding Motors.
They keep records too, you know.
I have no idea why he
came after me like that.
It was totally uncalled for
and, frankly, a little pathetic.
Mr. Matlock, will you tell
us what just happened?
Where did you get
your information?
- What are you gonna do now?
- Did you check the plate number?
How does it feel to make a
fool of yourself, Mr. Matlock?
Lousy!
Hey.
How does it feel to make a
fool of yourself, Mr. Matlock?
- Lousy!
- Mr. Matlock.
How does it feel to make a
fool of yourself, Mr. Matlock?
- Lousy!
- Lousy.
Saw the news?
The legendary Ben Matlock really
got cut down to size today, didn't he?
Heh-heh.
Being humiliated like
that really hurts, doesn't it?
And you know something? The pain
never goes away. It never goes away.
Every time you look in the mirror,
it comes back like a kick in the gut,
and you're never quite the same.
Councilwoman
Mendez and Bill Davis,
you humiliated them
before you killed them.
Put them out of their misery
is a better way to put it.
They were both lawyers.
Very good.
That mark on their forehead
wasn't the Roman numeral two.
No. No, it's Greek.
Upper case pi.
Plaintiff.
Little touch of irony.
No more talk.
Why lawyers?
Why not? More fun.
- Freeze! Go, go!
- Police officers.
I got him.
Don't move. Just stay
right where you are.
You thought I'd never know
you were coming for me.
But I pretty well had the
whole thing figured out.
- Do you know where he is?
- Yeah.
He's working at The Plant House.
I'm gonna see him today.
Maybe I should go with you.
No. I wanna see him alone.
I heard you were out of jail.
Mr. Matlock.
I didn't know you
were a plant lover.
How'd you get out
on parole so soon?
Well, the appeals court
threw out all the evidence.
I just was reading about you.
You're defending that guy
who blew up that judge's boat
and almost killed you.
He didn't do it.
So you gonna pull one of your
famous rabbits out of the hat
- and prove someone else did it?
- I might.
- I'd like to see that.
- Yeah. Maybe you will.
Yeah. I think whoever blew up the
boat was actually trying to kill me.
It was the same fellow who
broke in my house last night
and slipped on a
pair of Rollerblades.
Nearly broke his neck.
You think it was me?
Crossed my mind.
Oh, no, no, no. Mr. Matlock, no.
I was at home last night, alone.
You've gotta believe me.
I'm a changed man.
Where were you yesterday
afternoon about 5:15
when Ty Foster was killed?
I'm sorry. Who is Ty Foster?
Ty Foster is a fella who
unfortunately used to work for you.
He was killed in Willow Springs,
and I wanna know where you were.
Well, I don't think I know a
Ty Foster, but, uh, let me see.
Yesterday at 5:15...
I was involved in a car
accident over in Highgate
between 4:30 and 5:00.
You can check the police report.
And let me see, at rush hour,
that's gotta be at least 40
minutes from Willow Springs.
I didn't kill anyone,
Mr. Matlock.
I'm telling you, I'm
a changed man.
I'm sure.
I'll check with the police.
- I've been waiting for you.
- Oh.
I got the police report on Jeffrey
Spidel's accident yesterday.
He couldn't have gotten from
Highgate to Willow Springs
in time to kill Ty Foster.
Hm.
Well, remember the Baxter
University baseball cap
they found next to
Ty Foster's body?
Yeah.
It wasn't his.
The cap didn't fit his head,
and the hair inside wasn't his.
Oh.
What color was the hair?
Black and short.
I know a boy with black hair
who went to Baxter University.
Do you think it was his hat?
It could be,
but he was convicted of murder.
You have anything
to do with that?
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
A couple years ago, I
agreed to give a lecture
to the Law Club at
Baxter University.
It turned out to be one of
the biggest mistakes of my life.
Yeah, Mark?
Have you ever seen
the perfect murder?
Well, I've seen cases
that were never solved.
You really hate somebody
and you wanna kill them.
- How you do it?
- Yeah. How you do it.
How you do it. Theoretically,
if you wanted to kill somebody,
uh, you'd first have
to have a motive.
So you'd want to do it.
Then you'd find
somebody to kill.
- And you'd have to get rid of the body.
- Yeah.
You'd get rid of the body and
then try to frame somebody else.
One of the girls in my class
had just broken up with
a bully named Eddie Price
who everybody hated.
We're over? After
six months? No.
Hey, hey, you don't
seem to get it, do you?
She doesn't wanna see you
anymore. Just get out of her way.
You're beginning to annoy me.
I said move it.
- See you around.
- Mark.
Leave me alone.
Just leave me alone.
What the hell is going on?
Right after Eddie Price died,
the dean of students
called me to his office
and actually accused me
of teaching those kids how
to commit a perfect murder.
Ben, I think you
had a hand in this.
What did I do?
You all but gave
your class a blueprint
of how to commit
a perfect murder.
The police think I'm in on this?
Well, now, I didn't say
you did it intentionally.
I'm saying I
didn't do it at all!
Hey I saw you at
the café, Bobby.
For all I know, you might
be trying to frame me.
Bobby, I spoke to Buddy
Hart, Eddie's roommate.
He said you hated Eddie
because he took Carol from you.
Hated? Isn't that
a little overstated?
Bobby, you said
you wanted to kill him.
Time out here. Okay, I was madder
than hell when Carol first dumped me,
but that was a long time ago.
You may not believe this,
honey, but guys do get over you.
You know what? I don't like
being treated like a suspect.
Don't you get it?
We're all suspects.
Fortunately, what I told this
group turned out to be true.
There is no such thing
as a perfect murder.
Now, the night Eddie disappeared,
you were in your room studying.
Yes.
The proof we have of that is that
your car was parked down front.
That's right, it was.
Uh, well, how about Carol's
car that night? Did you drive it?
No. I didn't. I told you
I was at home, so...
Uh... Ahem.
This is the gas
pedal off Carol's car.
You see that shiny
spot right there?
Yeah, I see it.
I think that's varnish.
What about you?
- Could be.
- Yeah?
And, uh...
And this is, uh...
What are you doing with my shoe?
I borrowed it.
What the hell is going on?
I don't have to sit here
and answer your questions.
- I'm out of here.
- Hey. Hey, Bob. Bob.
- You got something to hide?
- No, but...
Then sit down. Answer
the man's questions.
You see this, uh, shiny spot here
on the bottom of your running shoe?
- I see it.
- I think that's varnish too.
I think it's the same varnish
that's on the gas pedal
from Carol's car.
Your uncle owns a
speedboat, doesn't he?
An old, uh, mahogany inboard?
Yeah, he does.
Are you aware that
on, uh, September 30th
at 5:00 in the evening,
a fresh coat of varnish
was applied to that boat?
No, I wasn't.
I believe the
varnish on that boat
is the same as the varnish
on your running shoe
and the gas pedal
from Carol's car.
That doesn't prove anything.
Well, I think... I think you...
I think you might
have killed Eddie.
I think you might have slipped
out of your apartment that night.
You didn't take your car
because you knew that
somebody might notice it was gone.
I think you might've used
the keys to Carol's car
that she gave you
when you were dating.
I think you may... Might
have driven her car
out of the parking lot at the
library over to Eddie's house,
killed him,
put him in the car,
driven him to the boat,
taken him out to sea
and dumped his body overboard.
You can't prove that
I killed Eddie Price.
Mr. Matlock, you can't
prove that Eddie's dead.
No.
No, I can't.
There's no body.
There may never be a body.
I was just making suppositions.
But I tell you, as sure
as we're all sitting here,
if I'm making
these suppositions,
the police will too.
Well, I'll find out where he is.
I might still have
his parents' number.
Let me see. Let me see.
Uh, Miss Simpson?
Ben Matlock.
Uh, I was calling
about your son.
No, I didn't.
I'm sorry.
Bye.
What happened?
Bobby Simpson got out
of prison four months ago.
And six weeks ago,
he was killed in an automobile
accident outside Miami.
Drunk driving.
Ben, if he's dead, what was
his hat doing at Ty Foster's?
Jeffrey Spidel.
He put it there.
He's toying with me.
It has to be Jeffrey Spidel.
Sure as I'm sitting
here, it's him.
I'm pretty sure Judge
Stern's boat was over there.
Hey, if you don't
mind me asking,
what do you care
where we kept the boat?
Oh. Uh, well, we figure the bomb
was put on the boat while it was here.
Not that we've ever
blown up anything,
but we figure the guy
had easier access on land
- instead of in the water.
- Uh-huh.
- Well, this is where it was.
- Huh.
I'd have never known the
judge had his boat up here
if he hadn't said he was
having it painted. Heh-heh.
Um...
Do you think you could
rope off this whole area
for the rest of the day?
- I guess.
- Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah.
Mr. Spidel, two years ago,
I accused you of murder,
and ultimately, you were
convicted. Remember that?
Yes, I was in prison for two years
before the case was thrown out.
How do you feel about me
since I was the one responsible
for sending you to prison?
Well, I think you were
just doing your job.
- No animosity?
- No, sir. None.
You ever feel like killing me?
Mr. Matlock, I'm
not angry with you.
I have come to
terms with all that.
I don't believe
that for a second.
Didn't you hire Ty Foster
to mug my friend Will Owens
so we would have to
cancel our fishing trip?
And didn't you have
Ty Foster take my client,
Glen Silver, to
lunch at the marina
so his fingerprints
would be found
in the vicinity of
Judge Stern's boat slip?
I told you, sir, I do
not know a Ty Foster.
As always, you were smart.
You did everything just right.
You chose Glen Silver to
frame for the judge's murder
because you knew that Glen
blamed the judge for disbarring him.
And the murder took place on
the anniversary of the disbarment.
You had everything pointed
at the judge as the target,
when all the time
you were trying to
murder me, weren't you?
I don't wanna murder anyone.
It should've worked.
Should've worked.
I went fishing with the
judge, the bomb went off,
but I got seasick
and got off the boat
before it happened.
Now the judge is dead.
Ty Foster works for you,
and he's probably
figured out what's going on.
So would you just tell
the court where you were
at 5:15 p.m., January 15th.
Well, as I told you, I was involved
in a car accident in Highgate.
It was rush hour.
You were about 45 minutes from
where you were to Ty Foster's house
when he was...
When he was killed.
This, uh, Baxter
University baseball cap
was found near the body.
It apparently belonged
to, uh, Bobby Simpson,
another young man I was
responsible for sending to prison.
Ever seen it before?
Mm... No, I don't think so. No.
Bobby was killed
about six weeks ago.
Car accident.
Of course you knew
that, didn't you?
No.
I think you did.
Get this. Somebody stole this
cap and placed it by the body.
- It was you, wasn't it?
- No.
I think it was. You
were toying with me.
You were waiting your
chance to get back at me.
When you stole his cap, you
also stole Bobby's motorcycle.
That's how you got across
town in rush-hour traffic.
You had the car
accident on purpose.
You had the motorcycle
hidden right there.
All you had to do was hop on it,
rush over to Ty's house and kill him.
- Right?
- No.
Objection. Irrelevant.
Your Honor, possibly
Mr. Matlock is confused.
He's trying the wrong case.
Your Honor, I apologize
for this digression.
But this man is a
cold-blooded killer.
And in time it will come
out that he killed Ty Foster.
But I intend to prove
that he killed Judge Stern.
- Make it snappy, Mr. Matlock.
- Yes, sir.
- You like boats, Mr. Spidel?
- Not particularly. No.
- Ever own one?
- No.
So you don't go to places like
marinas and boat shows and dry docks?
No, no, never.
What would you say if I
told you I had an eyewitness
who saw you at the
Harbor Dry Dock?
Well, I'd say he was a liar.
Heh. Yeah, you'd be right.
But I've got something better.
I don't know. Maybe it's
easier to put a bomb on a boat
when it's up on blocks
than in the water.
But I decided I'd make
a trip to Harbor Dry Dock
where Judge Stern's
boat was painted.
And there was paint
all around on the ground,
and you know how people
are, can't keep them out of it.
There was shoe prints here and
there, different shoes, different sizes.
And, uh, the police...
took this pair of shoes
from your place this morning.
And this is what the
police report says:
The report states that this
paint on the bottom of your shoe
is an exact match with
the blue bottom paint
used at the Harbor Dry Dock.
It also says that this
shoe is an exact match
with a print found in the
paint at the Harbor Dry Dock
right next to where Judge
Stern's boat was kept.
You were there, Mr. Spidel.
Probably at night.
You couldn't see the paint.
You planted the bomb
that killed the judge.
And you tried to kill me again.
And this time, if I have
anything to do with it,
I'm gonna send you to
prison for the rest of your life.
Golden slumber kiss your eyes
Smile await you when you rise
Sleep, pretty
baby, don't you cry
And I will sing
you lullaby Lullaby
Lullaby Lullaby
- Pretty.
- Oh, that's a beautiful lullaby.
- Yeah.
- There you go.
- Wow, you guys caught these?
- Yeah.
- You really caught them?
- Where'd you catch them?
- Crocker's Fish Market. Dig in.
www.tvsubtitles.net